[{"answer": "Hey. Super's in my bathroom changing my shower head. Have they changed your shower head", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Low flow? Well I don't like the sound of that. my friend exits", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm used to a 1200 mile buffer zone. I can't handle this. Plus I got the dinners, I got the pop ins. They pop in! It's brutal", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "The only way out of this is if my friend breaks up with his girlfriend and has to move back into the apartment and then they would have to go back to that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Not really", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Are you telling me there's not one condo available in all of that place", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That's right. They went like hotcakes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Got lucky", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Big news", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What? You're moving to that place!?! That's wonderful! I'm so happy!  For you! I'm so happy for you! Oh, what do you need this cold weather for", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What? You're moving to that place!?! That's wonderful! I'm so happy!  For you! I'm so happy for you! Oh, what do you need this cold weather for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "So you're moving there for spite", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh, every chance I get", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend? my friend! I'm busting! I'm busting", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "To spite my parents", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Hello. my friend's not here", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Just a second, I have to go to the bathroom", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What am I gonna do in the bathroom", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh please, Mrs. my friend, please", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well, one of those glasses", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, what am I gonna do it in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend's glasses", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah, a coffee cup's fine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes, fine, fine, a juice glass is perfect", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It doesn't matter", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shower-Head.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "A milk glass, a juice glass, any glass, just pick a glass", "qsentId": 30}]